おい　卓球たっきゅう台だいがあるじゃん
Hey, there is a table tennis table
いいね　あれやるか　あれ
That's good, let's play that, that game
古今ここん東西とうざい
Any time, any place
お題だいに答こたえて　球たまを打うつあれか
That game where you answer a question and hit the ball?
やるんなら罰ばつゲームを決きめようぜ
If we gonna play that, let's decide a penalty
じゃあ　うちの生徒せいと会長かいちょうを一発いっぱつ殴なぐる
How about... you have to punch our Student Council president once?
オーケー
Okay!
準備じゅんびいいか？
You guys ready?
３回かいミスしたら罰ばつゲームな
If you miss 3 time, you will be penalised
第だい１回戦かいせん　お題だいは
Round one, the topic is
天王星てんおうせいの衛星えいせいの名前なまえ！
The names of Uranus' satellites!
え？
Huh?
始はじめ！
Start!
アリエル！
Ariel!
ウンブリエル！
Umbriel!
チタニア！
Titania!
えっ　えっ　ええ　ええ
Eh eh eeh eeh
えっ
Eh
ちょ　ちょ　ちょっと待まって
W wai wait a second
問題もんだい難むずかしくない？
Isn't the question a bit too hard?
第だい２回戦かいせん
Round two
お題だいは　世界せかいの黒人こくじん大統領だいとうりょうの名前なまえ！
The topic is, name of Black presidents in the world
ケニア共和きょうわ国こく：　ムワイ･キバキ！
Republic of Kenya: Mwai Kibaki!
セネガル共和きょうわ国こく：　アブドゥライ･ワッド！
Republic of Senegal: Abdoulaye Wade!
オバマ
Obama
言いわれた！
He took it!
お前まえら！　打ち合うちあわせしてんだろ
Hey! You guys decided these ahead of time, right?
いや　全然ぜんぜん
No, not at all
もういい　俺おれに決きめさせろ
Enough, let me decide the question
いいよ　どうぞ
Sure, go ahead
俺おれの得意とくい分野ぶんやで攻せめる
I will attack with my field of specialty
国旗こっきに　月つきのマークが入はいっている国くにの名前なまえ！
Names of countries that have a moon in their flag!
マレーシア！
Malaysia!
チュニジア！
Tunisia!
アルジェリア！
Algeria!
パキスタン！
Pakistan!
マレーシアしか知しらねえし　俺おれ
Malaysia is all I know, dammit
何者なにものなんだよこいつら
What are these guys...
もういいよ　お前まえらの勝かちで
Whatever, you guys can take your win